{
    "id": "ed44b5b5858a4944ac8937a27eb9f368",
    "title": "Prepositions Worksheet",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Put a small quantity of sugar ………………… the batter.",
            "description": "Into is common after put to talk about directional movement. ",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "onto",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6851f1d6806343419c646e598588cda9"
        },
        {
            "question": "My quarrel is ……………………. the under-representation of women here.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "da96f93506504647a3f793d319bba8b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "A quarter of the population voted …………………… him.",
            "description": "You vote for or against somebody.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "385cf8d531cc4ffea6f809009d9cdd30"
        },
        {
            "question": "The restaurant offered us a quasi hamburger made ……………………. vegetables.",
            "description": "Made is used with of when we identify the material used to make something.",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "with",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1a5642e91e2d4dfaba8ac061fd0fe12d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Direct all queries ……………………… your nearest dealer.",
            "description": "To indicates direction. ",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "853cb891267145ffa496e5d65a20a32a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The police queried him ……………………….. his whereabouts the night of the crime.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "on",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4858949656a1426d8313b869a8e16bb8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Iced tea will quench your thirst ……………………… hot days.",
            "description": "We use on with days.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9f2343a678c54a15b9e68f6738328a65"
        },
        {
            "question": "The salesman pushed the product ………………………… every opportunity.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d4f46389c22345beb4ff7ba52dc7295e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The people shivered ………………………. fear when their village was invaded.",
            "description": "With is used in a number of expressions like shiver with, tremble with etc.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "from",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7e7de5ff6a9844718440a5dd09d7d229"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has a quality of kindness that appeals ……………………………. everyone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "at",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f7dea2abd7d245d6875a1f4b43c897c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Only applicants ………………………… the proper qualifications will be considered.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ab8cfe0f23c64771875ba7a090ee4fec"
        },
        {
            "question": "He had no qualms ………………………… robbing the poor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "about",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "466f0315d5a04c9fbb75d2c764b393cd"
        }
    ]
}